question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The movie 'Tron' received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The 2010 film 'The Social Network' is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "'Minions' was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The word 'Inception' came from the 2010 blockbuster hit 'Inception'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The original ending of 'Little Shop Of Horrors' has the plants taking over the world.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "Shaquille O'Neal appeared in the 1997 film 'Space Jam'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The Xenomorph from the science fiction film 'Alien' has acidic blood.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
